I have spent the last few weeks sharing
my journey with you all I recorded them
over a couple weeks in a couple sessions
as you can tell by the fact that my
wardrobe stays for you film event
changes and this is I guess the
conclusion video the last one although
I'm sure I will be adding more to this
playlist as I think of other things too
that are exactly part of my story I need
to fit in this one but this one I want
to talk about the perfection of my
journey and my story and how it all
comes together to make me me the
hindsight that I can access now that I
just reached 40 years old although it
didn't just come when I was 40 years old
it has been coming throughout my 20s and
my 30s of being able to look back and
see how my life has been impacted by
these single events and yet if they
weren't there I would be a completely
different person I would I would have
had different people in my life if I
hadn't been to that movie when I was a
teenager I would have had the
boyfriend's I had I wouldn't had the
friends I had if I hadn't had brain
tumors I wouldn't right now be able to
take the time to sit with my own
thoughts and create a world that works
for everyone I both wouldn't have the
capacity because I'd be doing something
completely different
and I wouldn't have the capacity because
I'd be working I wouldn't be on
disability at home unable to work if I
had known my whole life or for my
teenage years that I was queer or
autistic that would have been completely
different than learning them about that
when I was 36 and 39 respectively I if I
was employed if I had a partner I I
wouldn't have felt the freedom other
people can do both of those things and
be authentic but I wouldn't have felt
the freedom to be as authentic as I am
because I would have felt it what it
cost me my job I would have felt it
would have
Cosme relationships now I can see that
there's no payoff greater than being
your authentic self I'm gonna find my
purple I found my purpose but I'm gonna
find out how to make money on it and
then I won't be under the poverty line
on disability it doesn't mean I'm gonna
get over my disabilities but I will find
a way to make money from within my very
very limited capacity of the only thing
I can do is create an omni wind world
that is answered by the wrist that is
game B and works for everyone that is
what I'm here to do that is the capacity
I have to think big picture logic and
follow my path towards creating it to
share my story
well we create it with other people I
can see if the hindsight how every one
of my disabilities and health challenges
interweaves together to make me who I am
to be that my parenting the parts that
I'm amazing that the parts that I'm
definitely less amazing that in
combination make me the perfect parent
for my kid not because I'm perfect not
because I don't make mistakes but
because I'm the exact combination of
talent and challenge that is giving her
what she needs to be in this planet
helping her unfold to be her and her
mission her personality I can see in
hindsight and not even in hindsight
anymore I've experienced this so much
that even when I'm in the when I'm
depressed when I'm anxious when I'm
having a bad experience cuz life is
throwing me a curveball I know there's
something coming there's learning coming
and so I'm much more comfortable on the
roller coaster right now she's like cool
what's and what am I going to learn from
this so curiosity is this and when I get
the tension and the need to make this go
a very specific way I can love that
because I know there is something coming
from it in fact my whole lesson in life
is like can you accept yourself more can
you love yourself more for exactly who
you are without needing you to change
can you love others for who they are
without needing them to change can you
save this planet without needing it to
change
and that when I struggle with really I
how can you have it's a struggle it's a
clear struggle and yet yes I'm getting
there I am falling in love with this
planet exactly as it is because I can
see everybody is exactly who they are
supposed to be for the right combination
of people to come together and create
the tools and infrastructure and system
that works for them and then it works
for everybody we just have to allow it
to happen and we just have to start and
from where I'm sitting I get to be the
domino starts that and even if I don't I
am enjoying my journey and this journey
towards understanding myself and
standing for my vision even if I'm not
the one who gets to create it even if
it's just watching other people create
it we get to be alive at this moment in
history and I am loving watching it
unfold I have hope for a world that is
beautiful because I can see it and I can
see with all of my pessimism and realism
and logical mind that it was possible
enough to step into the whatever
metaphysical spiritual follow the next
step and let it prove itself to you I
get it doesn't make sense but it will
eventually miss of this whole journey
and that it's the viewer the people
involved they get to kind of make their
own judgement and although I know I'm
not the perfect person I'm constantly
owned I don't communicate this thing
well I mess up all of the time I also
know that's happening in its perfect way
because it's leading somewhere it's
unfolding as it's meant to be the right
people and right resources keep showing
up the universe keeps showing me it has
my back it has everyone's back it's here
- should teach you exactly what you're
here to learn you just have to start and
you already started he's have to realize
he started that it unfolds faster
I guess you don't even really need to do
that but I hope you get a bit of more of
my journey and so that you can kind of
follow along on the continual
progression forward because every week
all of these little things come about
and I feel like until you can get the
backstory of like these little instances
that have changed my entire life all of
these things that come together to make
me Jubilee Who I am to fulfill my
purpose you don't have to think that I'm
gonna forfeit my purpose you get to
watch it happen
I only 90 percent thing but I'm the
person who gets to do this
I keep creeping up and getting more and
more of it and like more like are you
sure like this is a little weird guys I
think why by the person because it isn't
somebody who's perfect who gets to do
this it isn't somebody who's charismatic
and comes off as powerful and leads us
all forward because then it wouldn't be
this this is everybody stepping forward
everybody realizing who they are is
exactly who they're supposed to be and
together we get to create a world that
works for everyone and now my soul
[Music]